{
  "2": [
    { "prompt": "мин", "answer": "булам" },
    { "prompt": "һин", "answer": "булаһың" },
    { "prompt": "ул", "answer": "була" },
    { "prompt": "булам", "answer": "мин" },
    { "prompt": "булаһың", "answer": "һин" },
    { "prompt": "була", "answer": "ул" }
  ],
  "3": [
    { "prompt": "мин", "answer": "бар" },
    { "prompt": "һин", "answer": "бар" },
    { "prompt": "ул", "answer": "бар" },
    { "prompt": "бар", "answer": "мин/һин/ул" }
  ]
}
